"As an AR associate, I need the ability to update invoice data (Insurance, CPN, Pricing, Customer Info, PO #, or Sales Tax), so that I can regenerate the invoice for the customer. _"	"Given I select an invoice from the AR Application, when I select it from the grid, then I should be able to open it in ""Edit Mode"" for saving corrections to it. Given I have make corrections to the invoice selected above, when I save my changes, then the invoice should be regenerated_with the changes I made."				
"As an AR associate, I need to be able to reprint invoices, so that I can provide it to a customer in need. Priority: Low Moscow: Must Have"	"Given I have made corrections to the invoice, when I search the AR Applicaiton, then the invoice should be regenerated_with the changes I made and available for Printing or Emailing."				
"As a German associate, I need to be able to provide and invoice/credit report to my external accountant, so that their system data matches GP data. Germany - As you may know we are working with an external accountant who is working with DATEV. He imports all our invoices and payments via an excel file which is based on the PC Man account numbers as you can see in the excel file attached. The file for invoices &credits is created by PC Man Accounting / Accounting Report Generator. The file of payments is created out of GP. I guess with PC Man sunset no more PC Man bill to numbers will exist? Datev account number have 6 digits starting with a 6. Is there any way to solve this problem? Besides the point reporting we would need a file (credits & invoices) like the one which is created by Accounting Report Generator as well. I [Germany AR] just have called Mr. Pachnerand got confirmed: as soon as we arrived at 6digits SNG bill to numbers these can be used ( as they start with 1XXXXX?) anddo not need to be –converted” Ä. this will be working up to 499999 after our AR test session 2 weeksago I just want to give you a small feedback on the meeting we had with Mr.Pachner last week concerning import of our invoice file to Datev. Datev account numbers have 6digits starting with a 6 but the number 5 would work as well. Until now the report of invoicescoming out PC Man (Accounting/C Accounting Report Generator) changed the 9 ofPC Man bill to numbers to 6 automatically: 923893 => 623893 As far as I understood correctlySGN bill to numbers will only be used in future. So Mr. Pachner came up with thefollowing solution: He will discontinue the PC Manaccount numbers at a special date & and set up the SGN ones starting with a5 (as the 6 already has been in use until now and we would need unique bill tonumbers ) and fill up 0 to 6 digits. __ SGN bill to _9947(until now shown in Datev as 623893- PC Man number 923893) -this would beentered to Datev with 509947Ä __ SGN bill to 1045 - thiswould be entered to Dated with 501045 Please, would it be possible tocreate the invoice file _ equivalent to the one we are using right now-_with the SGN bill to numbers converted automatically to what Datev needs?Would it be possible to make thischange at the end of 2015? If it will be done during thisyear this will probably cause big confusion on customers _& our sidewhen we send out requests for confirmation of balance due to the audit we willhave next year. Ann"	* Germany COID are able to generate reports from AR application that meet the same format as the attached * PO to add PCMan steps to get current report				
"As a customer I need my invoice to be generated and sent with the shipment, so that I can receive and pay the invoice when my package arrives Priority: High Moscow: Must Have Currently SABs are printed in Traffic on A4 paper, however, the printers in Traffic do have Letter sized paper in them in the event the SAB rendering is set for Letter printing."	Given a SAB customer has an invoice that needs to be printed in Traffic when the box is being labeled and stuffed then they can print the invoice.				
"Priority: High Moscow: Must Have As an AR associate, I need to know all inter-company shipments, so that I can create an inter-company invoice for each billing location at months end._ Everything shipped to a Samtec Entity within a given time period and mark up the price up by 3%."	"Given the AR associate wishes to generate a Misc Debit / Credit for Interco Billing to another Samtec Entity, when they run a report for Interco Billing then the Appropriate Misc AR data should be provided."				
Priority: High Moscow: Should Have As an AR associate I want the ability to click on an Add/Edit function to add a credit to an invoice or edit the invoice when I find it in the search grid so that I get a form to make my changes or enter the credit.	"Given the Invoice needs to be corrected, when I search for it in the AR grid, then I should be able to select it and have a Button or Link_for Add/Edit."				
Priority: High Moscow: Must Have As a customer I want my invoice provided in my preferred method (probably email) at the time my order is placed by CS.	"Given an order is placed on SGN and the customer preference is proforma then email the accounting group the rendered invoice. Given the order is credit card and the invoice preference is Proforma_then when the invoice number is generated it will add a ""CC"" at the end of the sequential invoice number. Given the order is prepaid_and the invoice preference is Proforma_then when the invoice number is generated it will add a ""PP"" at the end of the sequential invoice number. Given the order is PP or CC and the Proforma invoice was generated/sent, then when the shipment occurs that Proforma invoice should have the Shipment ID, Tracking number and Shipment date should be populated to that invoice record."				
"Priority: Medium Moscow: Must Have As a Traffic associate I should be able to regenerate the documentation (Invoice, Commercial Invoice) for a recently packaged SAB that was missing a parcel so that I can send out the shipment with the correct number of parcels included."	"Given the shipment has been processed and a SAB invoice printed, when I discover that I missed a parcel that should be part of the shipment then I should be able to reverse the previously printed documentation and record locks so that I can add the additional parcel and reprint the invoice and other documentation from the Traffic area without anyone else's support (PCMan team)."				
Priority: High Moscow: Should Have Actions: Edit or Delete As a Misc Billings Clerk I want the ability to edit or delete a Misc Billing document record from the AR application so that I can fix it or delete it before it is submitted to the Credit Authorization Queue.	"Given I see a Misc Billing record when I select the record, then I should be provided an Edit/Delete button or Edit/Delete links."				
Priority: Medium Moscow: Must Have as an_AR associate I want to be able to enter a customer name change on the invoice rendering so that I can save it and send it to the customer for payment.	"Given I select an invoice from the AR Application, when I select it from the grid, then I should be able to open it in ""Edit Mode"" for saving corrections to it. Given I have make corrections to the invoice selected above, when I save my changes, then the invoice should be regenerated_with the changes I made."				 